kpopmart.com 2016-06-25

# privacy and security - Kpop Mart

**PRIVACY & SECURITY**

**1\. Privacy** ﻿

Kpopmart.com is committed to protecting your privacy. We hope that you will take the time to read this policy, which explains what information we collect from you and how we use that information. By using our website or by purchasing products or services from us, you agree to be bound by this policy. Please check back frequently, as this policy may change from time to time. ﻿

**Information You Give Us** ﻿

We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. ﻿

**How We Protect Your Information** ﻿

To protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control, we have implemented security measures at this website. When you place orders or access your account information, a secure server is employed. All information you input is encrypted by the secure server layer (SSL) before it is sent to us and all the customer data we collect is similarly protected against unauthorized access.﻿

**E-mail Communication & Newsletter**﻿

To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from us if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.﻿

**Our Use of Cookies** ﻿

"Cookies" are small files of data that reside on your computer and allow us to recognize you as a customer if you return to our site using the same computer and browser. We send a "session cookie" to your computer if and when you log in to your account by entering your ID and password. These cookies allow us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages in our site during the same session, so that you don't need to re-enter your password multiple times. Once you log out or close your browser, these session cookies expire and no longer have any effect. ﻿

**Children** ﻿

At Kpopmart.com, we believe that the privacy of children is important. We do not monitor the age of our user audience except in connection with surveys and contests, and except for age data optionally provided by users who wish to customize their account preferences, however, visitors and users under the age of thirteen (13) should not submit personal identifying information to Kpopmart.com without the consent of their parent(s) or guardian(s). If a user is under the age of thirteen (13) the user may not, even under the supervision of a parent or guardian, make any submissions of content to Kpopmart.com.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Please check back frequently, as this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. In the event of a material change to the Privacy Policy, for a reasonable time after such change we will add "Updated", "New", or a similar term near the link to the Privacy Policy on the home page of Kpopmart.com and elsewhere, as applicable, throughout our website﻿

**2\. Security** ﻿

Kpopmart.com is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. Your credit card and bank account information are stored only in encrypted form on computers that are not connected to the Internet. We restrict access to your personally identifiable information to employees who need to know that information in order to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with any related regulations to guard your nonpublic personal information. We test our security systems regularly and also contract with outside companies to audit our security systems and processes.﻿
